This is a podcast called The I'm so
excited
to
see you
in the next video.
I'm not alone, you miss no, I'm not alone
Earlier this morning,
the body of an unidentified male was found
in the Konda River in Chioda City, Tokyo.
The remains were badly mutilated,
and police are working to identify
the deceased as soon as possible.
Man, it's crazy in here. So busy.
You know, you could help
around here as well, Chief.
If we don't have enough hands, I
could always hire some new mates.
Are you sure we're allowed to do that?
Well, we are raking it in,
thanks to the Lady Omoe effect.
If that's the case, you should
stop talking and get us some help.
I get to have some noobies?
Hey, welcome back.
Oka, Oka, Oka.
It's Okachimachi!
No way.
That's such a horrible way to go.
So, oh, Okachimachi's been
offed on so, oh. How could they?
Hey, that doesn't spell radio anymore.
It's more like Rady Panda.
The head, it's empty?
You're the one inside the suit?
You're alive, then.
You have something on your head.
This note is to notify
you that the Oinky Doink
Cafe is hereby disowned
from the Creatureland group.
Huh?
You're kidding, let me see that.
It's legit.
This can't be.
This is all just a
really bad dream, right?
Damn it!
I can't get through!
Nobody's answering the damn phone!
If Creatureland disowns
us, we won't survive here.
Just when our sales are
growing, thanks to Lady Omoe.
Why would they do this?
Yeah, what is wrong with them?
What's going to happen now?
They'll be coming for us.
Chief, what are we going to do?
Don't expect me to answer everything!
Think for yourself, stupid piglet!
I can't come up with anything!
Well, me neither!
We're really just helpless
little piggies now.
In this cage we call Akiba,
we're just sitting here waiting
for the day we get slaughtered.
Man, I didn't plan on dying this young.
How could they?
You're still only just 36, Ronko.
It's okay, Nagomi.
I'm filled with doubt all the time.
Nagomen. Huh? Good morning.
Sorry, the cafe still isn't ready.
Do you remember Akai? Huh? Of course.
He was the one who was
always dressed in red, right?
That's him.
He's dead.
You know the body they
found in the Kanda River?
That was Akai. Huh?
The police say he may have been tortured.
Sounds like a maid did it.
Wait, what?
You're kidding, right?
A maid wouldn't go up
out murdering a master?
He liked to brag about you
when we were at other cafes.
Please, the maids there
weren't happy about that.
He was kind of oblivious to it all.
Honestly, we're scared too.
I think they might have us
pegged as oinky-doink regulars.
Sorry, we can't come home
to oinky-doink anymore.
We can't be fans if we're freakin' dead.
Goodbye!
Hello masters, welcome home to the pig.
We're so sorry.
Our cafe has a strict no maids policy.
What do you mean, Piglet?
We're just regular meaustresses.
It's so obvious that you're maids.
I spy some dashing masters
sitting right here.
I hope you don't mind if we join.
Well, hey, that's mine!
This isn't fit for drinking.
I know some better cafes that
don't serve this kind of slop.
Come on, let's skip this joint.
No, sorry, I'm...
Whose master do you think
you're harassing here?
Oh, Moe, someone's scary. Seriously?
Um, hey, we have to go
now, actually. Oh, okay.
I hope you come home again, my master.
Uh, um, yeah.
Now this is what a true
pigsty should look like.
What's going on? Huh?
Why are you doing this?
A Dazzlion was supposed to be the
next lady of Moe at the festival.
You're the smelly oinkers
who ignored that rule.
What?
This is all because I
am the next lady in Moe?
So what if it is? Huh?
If we're disowned, you're our enemy.
Fine by me. Wanna go? Now?
Pranko, what do you think you're doing?
The 40-year-old maid seems
to know what's what. Bye!
We'll be back tomorrow.
Pranko, why did you stop me?
You're getting soft on us?
It's all because of me.
I'm the one to blame for
Oinkidouin getting disowned.
Huh?
When I was younger,
I made an oath of sisterhood with the
current head of the Creatureland group.
What?
Is that the sister you
told me about before?
Yes, she's the one.
We used to work together a long time ago.
For real?
Yeah, for real.
In the 1960s, there was
a maid named Miss Michio,
who was a formidable force in Akiva.
The place where Oinky Doink
Cafe is now used to be a maid
cafe founded by Miss Michio
called the Maid Tea House.
The head and I worked as maids there.
She was the one who mentored
me and taught me everything
back when I had very little
experience as a maid.
However, as close as we were, we regretfully
clashed over the cafe's policies.
I believe the head has disowned our
cafe due to her contempt for me.
Hey pops, I need a reload!
Tomorrow I shall go and
settle this properly.
You can't go by yourself.
This is all because I stole
the Lady Omoe title Sorry,
this fight is just
between me and the head.
I can't drag you all into
it Why in the world would
anybody from our cafe think
you dragged us into this,
right?
Huh?
Yuka, live out your responsibility.
We won't ever forget you, Runko.
I shall do that.
This isn't right!
Don't you all agree?
Do you know any other way?
At this rate, we're all just
gonna be slaughtered pigs.
You're kidding me, right?
We don't have what it
takes to protect her.
Though it sucks to admit it. Zoya!
If we go, that means we undermine Bronco's
resolve to end this with her sister.
Fine, forget it!
Even if it's just me!
Are you prepared to die?
If not, you'll just get in my way.
It will be an early morning for me
tomorrow, so I'll take my leave now.
Hey, Pops, all the best.
Ever since she met you, girl,
she actually looked like she was
enjoying herself for the first time.
You know, she's desperate
about protecting all of you.
Though she doesn't know how to show it.
What the hell you can't go there without
your star player we can't just abandon you?
For going to call
ourselves mushrooms we need
to get into business
let's show him the power
of a true bond now you're
changing your mind you
may lose your lives
though bronco i'm prepared
i'm not prepared to die
just yet but to make sure
all of us come back to
the oinky-doink together
all of you then thank you so very much.
How do I look today?
Your skin is glowing in a way that
befits the top of the ecosystem.
Good.
What do you think you're doing, please?
Do you have any idea
who's behind these doors?
You're coming with us, furball.
All right all of you out and leave
your weapons ignore them and fill
these big heads full of Life you hear
me what are y 'all standing around
for get the hell out if you're
gonna kill me then Do it now you're
all hostage you pathetic porkers
shouldn't be picking a fight with the
king of Beasts my horoscope totally
sucked today do you think i'm gonna
die nah we'll be fine female
Intuition yeah let's go with that boss
please excuse me the swine have taken
a hostage and Shot themselves in
da's lion kill them but boss you
personally managed as lion kill them
Yes madam creature
You yes ma 'am
There's so many of them
leaving let's go right
There's like a ton of them
If you value Simba's life
Don't they care at all about the hostage?
What the hell?
Come on, man!
Good old Miss Snoggy.
We're all going to hell
together, fucking swine!
Don't let them faze you.
We can't let them near us.
I'm going to kill all of you.
No one's here.
Do you think everyone
headed over to Dazzline?
It says the CEO is on the top floor.
So if it isn't Ronk O'Manen...
No way.
Hand over your guns.
She's waiting for you upstairs.
I wouldn't dream of getting out
of here alive if I were you.
Excuse me, Miss Nagi. They're here.
Shall we then? Yes.
Allow me to return these.
Please forgive me, mistress.
I'm sorry I took the Lady Omoe title.
Truthfully, I thought I could
never have won it that easily.
Look at me. Huh?
Ranko, why are you here?
To ask you to reconsider
disowning Oinky Doink.
So that means you're not here to kill me?
I did want to kill you.
But I realize now that I can't do it.
If at all possible, I would
rather not kill you either.
Uzuko.
Ranko, I can get you a seat
with the higher-ups. What?
So long as you can prove your sincerity.
You must go kill the lazy
swine at Oinky Doink. What?
I know you're deeply desperate
to protect the pigsty,
just because you can't get over
what happened to Miss Michio.
It's time to let go.
From now on, you must
fight to protect me, Ronko.
I'm sure Miss Michio would understand.
Working under me will get you everything.
Security in Akiba.
Respect from the other maids.
Masters with wealth.
I'll provide you with all of that.
We can be in the maid
business together again.
I must apologize.
I can't do that.
Why not?
To be honest, Oinky Doink
Cafe means the world to me.
Allow me to give my life in exchange
for letting Oinky Doink off the hook.
Runko!
You promised we would go home together!
I find this hard to believe.
Uzuko, Akiba is going to
need a cafe like Oinky Doink.
A cafe that can't even
squeeze out their dues.
I think an indignant person like you would
truly benefit by visiting the Oinky Doink.
Be careful with your
choice of words. Franco!
What's so special about that pigsty?
I enjoy it there.
We all went to the casino together.
and played a baseball game.
They threw a party on my birthday and
everyone sang and celebrated it with me.
And I've gotten much better
at catch-up doodling.
You enjoy it?
That's too funny.
You there. Yes.
Those crab pincers on your head.
Lock them off.
Please leave Nogomi out of this.
Okay, I will gladly.
Nogomi, you can't do it!
Bronco, please let me do my share.
Zoya!
I can't stop the bleeding!
I guess this is it, piglets.
I don't want to watch
you all get slaughtered.
I'll see you on the other side, my babies.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
I'm so glad I was a part
of Oinky Doink Cafe.
A manager can't give up that easily.
Ronko and Nogomi are out there fighting.
Isn't Oinky Doink your cafe?
My cafe?
Die, bitches!
You're not gonna mess with my damn cafe!
Allow me to lock off one of my pigtails.
Ranko,
is the pigsty special to you because this
maid here somehow got under your skin?
What?
Tell me, what does she have to offer?
Answer me now.
Everything.
She reminds me of Miss Michio.
Nogami!
Power is everything in Akiba.
A maid with no power
has no worth to anyone.
Uzuko, please!
If we kept listening to Miss Michio,
we would have been massacred.
You know that now.
That's why you've lived
your life killing maids.
Make your choice.
Me or her. Which one?
No!
No, Ronko!
You can't do this!
Isn't she a one and only sworn sister?
Please, Ronko!
Shoot me, or else she dies.
I can't choose.
They're both too precious and dear to me.
Like family I never had.
Ussuko.
Please let them off in
exchange for my life!
Oikidoin Cafe.
Is my only home.
Here you are, an old warthog,
on your knees crying.
Please, I beg you?
They're worth shedding tears over? Yes.
You disappoint me.
Forget it.
Huh?
What do you want from us?
You need to squeeze out at least ten
times more of the honey money from now on.
Then the oinky-doink is not disowned,
and you'll let us pay off our dues
if we pay ten times more honey money?
You want to die? No! I'm sorry!
We will! We'll squeeze it out!
Thank you, Usuko.
From now on, you're nothing but livestock
working your asses off for the group.
I've had enough.
Now get the hell out.
Please excuse us.
Sometime, come see my work as a maid.
Boinky Doink Cafe is epic to
serve as a home to all masters.
As if I would ever go to a pigsty.
Listen up! Huh?
I got a message from our heads!
What are you doing?
Shoot her!
Now!
She's unarmed, Chief.
I said shoot her!
The fighting is over!
I got a damn hole in my pouch.
Dude, the fighting is over. Don't shoot.
Don't nobody shoot.
Your hair tie.
I'm afraid that it got ruined.
Huh?
Oh, that's okay.
I can just buy another one.
Yeah, you're right.
Hi everyone you're all
alive we were so totally
close to dying so what happened she let us
off as long as we pay 10 times more honey
money for real how are
we gonna do that we never
even paid our regular
dues on time couldn't you
have haggled for less
no way that whole ordeal
was terrifying you should be grateful I'll
work really hard everyone
I want to welcome you
home to the pigsty.
Super cute!
This one's cute, but I think this
one would look good on her too.
Would you like
to take that?
Yes, could you please wrap it as a gift?
I think this one might look cute
An ambulance, please!
Call an ambulance, please!
Someone call an ambulance!
Oh, Ronco.
I want to be a cute maid.
Save your breath, Ronco.
A cute little maid.
You're already a wonderful maid, Ronco.
A maid I really look up to.
I want to keep doing
this with all of you.
Ronco...
That's a matter of life.
You're going to see the truth.
You're going to see the blood.
I'm going to cry.
I'm not sure how to do it.